Freshman Directory UP173
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Freshman Directory
1953 -- 2007
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Student Resources
UP173
0.75 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Freshman Year Book. It was published by Sword and Shield, the Sophomore Class Honor Society, showing pictures of all students in the class with home towns. Later, Tufts Students Resources took over publication. The Freshman Directory became the First-Year-Student Record, then the Freshman Record, then the New Student Record, and as of 2011 is the Freshman Facebook.
Related Materials
UA163, Tufts Student Resources, DCA
Biographical / Historical
TSR is a semi-autonomous, non-profit, student-run business organization founded in 1981 at Tufts University whose primary goals include: Providing the University community with needed services and goods. Offering employment and work-study opportunities to Tufts University students. Providing a medium in which students can gain business management and entrepreneurial experience without the investment of personal capital. Tufts Student Resources has been providing the Tufts community with the goods, services, employment, and business experience all while maintaining its status of being student-run. Advised by a Board of Directors, consisting of representatives from the Dean of Students, Student Activities, Student Employment, and other departments of the University, TSR has established itself as entirely financially independent of the University. In addition, TSR has become one of the most important organizations on campus. TSR currently encompasses seven divisions declaring annual revenues of $180,000 while employing approximately 60 students.
- Freshman Directory, 1953 -- 2007; 1959 -- 1971; UP173.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Freshman Year Book. It was published by Sword and Shield, the Sophomore Class Honor Society, showing pictures of all students in the class with home towns. Later, Tufts Students Resources took over publication. The Freshman Directory became the First-Year-Student Record, then the Freshman Record, then the New Student Record, and as of 2011 is the Freshman Facebook.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Freshman Yearbook, Class of 1957, 1953; UP173.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1958, 1954; UP173.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1960, 1956; UP173.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1961, 1957; UP173.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1963, 1959; UP173.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1964, 1960; UP173.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1965, 1961; UP173.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1966, 1962; UP173.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1967, 1963; UP173.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1968, 1964; UP173.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1969, 1965; UP173.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1971, 1967; UP173.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1972, 1968; UP173.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1973, 1969; UP173.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Directory, Class of 1974, 1970; UP173.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Directory of Entering Students, Class of 1975, 1971; UP173.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Entering Students Directory, Class of 1977, 1973; UP173.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1986, 1982; UP173.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1987, 1983; UP173.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1988, 1984; UP173.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1989, 1985; UP173.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1962, 1958; UP173.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Members of the Class of 1970, Freshman Directory, 1966; UP173.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Freshman Directory, Class of 1996, 1992; UP173.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University First-Year-Student Record, Class of 1998, 1994; UP173.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University Freshman Record, Class of 2002, 1998; UP173.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2003, 1999; UP173.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2004, 2000; UP173.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2005, 2001; UP173.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2006, 2002; UP173.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2007, 2003; UP173.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University Freshman Record, Class of 2000, 1996; UP173.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2008, 2004; UP173.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2010, 2006; UP173.001.002.00011.000001 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University New Student Record, Class of 2011, 2007; UP173.001.002.00011.000002 (Box 2)